good evening everyone. Um
hopefully everybody is doing well. Um
just want to let you know that this is
not going to be uh an extended
um video. Uh I'm actually just jumping
on uh to make an announcement about
photo theology in seven days. So some of
you are um
aware of my photo theology in seven days
class.
There's also the Daniel in seven seven
days class and the revelation in seven
days class.
Um we've actually gone through a cycle
of each of these classes and um the next
cycle
uh for the photoology
course begins in two days.
So it's actually supposed to begin a
little bit earlier uh actually last um
last Sunday, but we're going to be
starting this Friday instead. So, for
those of you that have been asking, did
the class start?
Uh, is it too late to sign up? The
answer is no to both of those. Okay. Uh,
you can still sign up for the course.
Uh, we're going to be starting, like I
said, Friday night. And for those of you
who are unaware,
this is uh a 7-day how to study the
Bible course.
Um I'm teaching it live and uh it's
going to be two hours every evening. So,
beginning Friday night, um this Friday,
Saturday, uh for seven days, we're going
to be going through the photo theology
palace. If you've listened to my
sermons, if you've listened to me
preach, if you've listened to my
teaching,
um the photoology principle basically
summarizes,
I shouldn't say summarize, basically
details how I study the Bible. Um, and
so I'm teaching that
seven days, two hours a day. That's 14,
excuse me, 14 hours of teaching, y'all.
14 hours of teaching. Um
and what we're doing in this class is we
are going through there are 38 floors in
this palace what I call the photo
theology palace. Um
these 38 rooms all represent different
principles of photo theology. And the
basic idea behind it is that you could
take any verse
uh any text you're studying, any
parable, any prophecy and actually
funnel it through 38 different ways.
Let me say it this way. 38 different
ways you can look at that one text.
And remember that's 38 rooms. Some of
these rooms have five, six, seven
principles
in uh within the room. Uh so for
example,
one of the rooms that we have is the um
that's in the palace is the blue room um
which is code for sanctuary room. And in
the sanctuary room, we basically learn
how to take a verse and funnel it
through all six articles of furniture in
the sanctuary. So, it's really learning
to apply the scriptures
in ways that you never would have
thought, ways that you never would have
imagined. Like, if I were to say to you,
hey, take John 3:16 and I want you to
look at John 3:16 in the context of the
table of showbread. Now, look at John
3:16 in the context of the altar of
sacrifice. Look at John 3:16 in the
altar of the in the in the um context of
the labor. Look at John 3:16 in the
context of the table of the uh altar or
the um altar of incense. Look at John
3:16 within the context of the seven
branch candlestick and look at John 3:16
in the context of the ark of the
covenant.
Those are six different studies that as
you are looking at that one verse in six
different ways, you're going to see
things that you may have never I never
thought about that before. I never
thought to connect John 3:16 with the
ark of the covenant or with the altar of
incense. So that is just one example. In
other words, it's not really just 38
ways to look at the verse. Um, it's an
infinitely greater number
because after you finish moving that
verse through all of those different
principles and you come up with a you
you you're leaving that room with a
thought that you didn't have going into
that room, you cannot take that new
thought and funnel it again through all
38 rooms and through all the principles
that come with it. So,
that's just kind of like a rough idea of
what this photoology course is about,
what the class is about. Um, again, the
class will begin uh this Friday night, 7
p.m. The website, if you want to
register for the class, if you want to
sign up for this course, um, is
myphototheology.com.
Okay? my photoology.com.
Go to that site. You're going to see
three classes. There is the Daniel in
seven days class. There is the
Revelation in seven days class. And
there is the photo theology in seven
days class. We're dealing we're are
going to be doing the photo theology in
seven days first.
Now,
uh, for those of you that sign up for
this class,
you are going to get a sneak peek at,
yes, I'm about to say it,
the new
photo theology app.
You will be among the first to see this
app. So now I know that you are probably
aware of the photoology GPT. This is
different. This is an app and uh it is
fire y'all. That's all I'm going to say.
It is fire. Anyway, um so that's it
everyone. I just wanted to let you know
um photo theology my photoology
um at myphototheology.com.
Sorry, myphototheology.com. And that's
where you go to sign up. Sign up for the
photo theology class, the Daniel class,
and revelation class will come at later
dates. Uh and I'll make those
announcements as well. Um but uh that's
it everyone. That's it. So hopefully uh
I will see you in class this Friday. Uh
it is live and by the way uh you will
get PDFs. Um you will have access to the
recording. So, if there's a day that you
or a night that you're unable to make,
um it will all be recorded, you'll have
access to it. This is an interactive
class, so you get to ask me questions.
Um the whole thing, it's all live. So,
uh with that said, guys, uh go to the
website myphototheology.com,
sign up, and I will see you Friday
night. God bless you.